<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Cloudmesh Community</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Cloudmesh Community</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Gregor von Laszewski, 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 01:42:40 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmesh Pi Burn</title>
      <link>/project/cloudmesh-pi-burn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 01:42:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cloudmesh-pi-burn/</guid>
      <description>cm-burn is a program to burn many SD cards for the preparation of building clusters with Raspberry Pi&amp;rsquo;s. The program is developed in Python and is portable on Linux, Windows, and OSX. It allows users to create readily bootable SD cards that have the network configured, contain a public ssh key from your machine that you used to configure the cards. The unique feature is that you can burn multiple cards in a row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmesh Nist</title>
      <link>/project/cloudmesh-nist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 01:42:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cloudmesh-nist/</guid>
      <description>We identify interfaces that are instrumental for the interaction with Clouds, Containers, and High Performance Computing (HPC) systems to manage virtual clusters to support the NIST Big Data Reference Architecture (NBDRA). The REpresentational State Transfer (REST) paradigm is used to define these interfaces, allowing easy integration and adoption by a wide variety of frameworks.
Refernces 1.NIST Big Data Interoperability Framework: Volume 8, Reference Architecture Interfaces PDF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmesh Graphql</title>
      <link>/project/cloudmesh-graphql/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 01:41:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cloudmesh-graphql/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmesh Client</title>
      <link>/project/cloudmesh-client/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 01:41:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cloudmesh-client/</guid>
      <description>Cloudmesh client is a simple client to enable access to multiple cloud environments form a command shell and commandline. It is grown out of the need to simplify access to multiple clouds for researchers and students easily. In contrast to our earlier versions of cloudmesh it explicitly separates the code to only target client code. Due to this simplification it is also possible to install the client code not only on Linux, OSX, but also Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>